

# WOJCIECH ŁASKA

FRONT-END DEVELOPER

### **SKILLS**

- TypeScript
- JavaScript
- Pvtho
- HTMI
- CSS / SASS
- AWS
- PostgreSQL
- GIT
- Angula
- React
- React Native
- Redux
- RxJS
- Diango
- Diango Rest Framework
- Flask
- Polish native
- English B2

#### **PORTFOLIO**

<u>wl-portfolio.pl</u> <u>linkedin.com/in/wojciech-laska-pl</u> <u>github.com/wojlas</u>

#### CONTACT

+48 733 145 054 wojciech.laska.01@gmail.com

ul. Ogródki 21 44-230 Bełk

#### **ABOUT ME**

I have been working as a front-end developer in angular for more than two years, but I discovered my passion for programming much earlier, as early as middle school. I am currently knowledgeable about front-end concepts and technologies, as well as in the back-end and databases, and I am learning about the AWS cloud. Privately, I like sports, especially football and cycling, music and also technology in any edition.

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

## Front-end developer

CreateCtrl Poland (05.2022 - present)
Development of the frontend layer of the REST product. Working closely with the backend team, UI/UX, product management to achieve the best results in the shortest possible time. Working with angular, HTML, SASS, AWS, GIT.

## **Delivery car driver**

FPH Multipak s.j (11.2013 - 05.2022)
Daily cooperation with the end customer, responsibility for the goods and the vehicle, keeping the vehicle in good technical and hygienic condition.

## **EDUCATION**

Coders Lab - programming school Front-end React Developer (11.2021 - 02.2022)

Advanced JavaScript, React, Redux

Coders Lab - programming school Python Developer (03.2021 - 10.2021)

Python, PostgreSQL, Django, Django Rest, Flask, JavaScript, Pytest, Pytest Django, SCRUM, GIT

**ZSBI in Żory** IT Technician (09.2009 - 05.2013)

Fundamentals of programming, operating system management, internal and external networking, computer design, basics of computer graphics.